Register of the Walter E. Shjeflo papers
Hoover Institution Archives
Walter E. Shjeflo papers
1950-1985
2004C53
Hoover Institution Archives
33 manuscript boxes (13.2 linear feet)
This collection contains correspondence, legal records, and printed matter relating to efforts to determine the fate and resolve the legal status of American servicemen captured or missing in action during the Vietnam War. Includes copies of military records and other government documents released under the Freedom of Information Act.
Shjeflo, Walter E.
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 2004.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical Note
American lawyer; attorney for families of American servicemen captured or missing in action in the Vietnamese War.
Scope and Content of Collection
Correspondence, legal records, and printed matter relating to efforts to determine the fate and resolve the legal status of American servicemen captured or missing in action during the Vietnam War. Includes copies of military records and other government documents released under the Freedom of Information Act.
Prisoners of war.; United States--Armed Forces--Vietnam.; Vietnam War, 1961-1975--Missing in action.; Vietnam War, 1961-1975--Prisoners and prisons, North Vietnamese.
- Correspondence, 1958-1984
  - 60 Minutes, 1979 (Box-folder 1: 1)
  - Abblitt, W., 1958-1968 (Box-folder 1: 2)
  - Abshire, David, 1971 (Box-folder 1: 3)
  - Ainsworth, Thomas, 1971-1981 (Box-folder 1: 4)
  - Allord, Gary, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 1: 5)
  - Anderson, David, 1980 (Box-folder 1: 6)
  - Anderson, H., 1973 (Box-folder 1: 7)
  - Anderson, John, 1979 (Box-folder 1: 8)
  - Atkinson, George, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 1: 9)
  - Bacon, Andrew, 1980 (Box-folder 1: 10)
  - Bacon, John, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 1: 11)
  - Bailey, George, 1979 (Box-folder 1: 12)
  - Baker, Hazel, 1966 (Box-folder 1: 13)
  - Baker, Patsy, 1973 (Box-folder 1: 14)
  - Ballard, Bobby, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 1: 15)
  - Banner, Roy, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 1: 16)
  - Barton, Myra, 1980 (Box-folder 1: 17)
  - Bauer, George, 1981 (Box-folder 1: 18)
  - Beller, Bruce, 1977 (Box-folder 1: 19)
  - Bentson, Lloyd, 1979 (Box-folder 1: 20)
  - Bevier, R., 1968-1969 (Box-folder 1: 21)
  - Blackburn, Donald, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 1: 22)
  - Blake, Harry, 1975 (Box-folder 1: 23)
  - Boardman, Norman, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 1: 24)
  - Bond, M., 1980 (Box-folder 1: 25)
  - Bond, Peggy, 1980 (Box-folder 1: 26)
  - Bosiljevac, T., 1978 (Box-folder 1: 27)
  - Brock, John, 1980 (Box-folder 1: 28)
  - Brom, Theodore, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 1: 29-30)
  - Bronars, E., 1979 (Box-folder 1: 31)
  - Brooks, George, 1980 (Box-folder 1: 32)
  - Brown, George, 1974 (Box-folder 1: 33)
  - Brzezinski, Zbigniew, 1977 (Box-folder 1: 34)
  - Bull, James, 1965 (Box-folder 1: 35)
  - Burkhalter, E., 1981 (Box-folder 1: 36)
  - Carleton, Joseph, 1970 (Box-folder 1: 37)
  - Case, Robert, 1972 (Box-folder 1: 38)
  - Chapman, L., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 1: 39)
  - Clowers, E., 1966 (Box-folder 1: 40)
  - Cochran, 1967 (Box-folder 1: 41)
  - Colgan, John, 1977 (Box-folder 1: 42)
  - Collins, Edward, 1978 (Box-folder 1: 43)
  - Conley, Thomas, 1979 (Box-folder 1: 44)
  - Constantino, Thomas, 1979 (Box-folder 1: 45)
  - Cook, Joel, 1979 (Box-folder 1: 46)
  - Cooke, D., 1980 (Box-folder 1: 47)
  - Corbett, W., 1966 (Box-folder 1: 48)
  - Corbin, Thomas, 1965 (Box-folder 1: 49)
  - Cornelius, Fay, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 1: 52)
  - Coskey, K., 1976 (Box-folder 1: 51)
  - Coveleskie, John, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 1: 52)
  - Crabtree, Carol, 1980 (Box-folder 1: 53)
  - Cranston, Alan, 1979 (Box-folder 2: 1)
  - Creed, Susan, 1973 (Box-folder 2: 2)
  - Cressman, Evelyn, 1984 (Box-folder 2: 3)
  - Cromwell, Lawrence, 1975 (Box-folder 2: 4)
  - Cunliffe, William, 1978 (Box-folder 2: 5)
  - Cushman, R., undated (Box-folder 2: 6)
  - Daniels, R., 1972 (Box-folder 2: 7)
  - Daskalakis, J., 1967 (Box-folder 2: 8)
  - Decker, Loren, 1981 (Box-folder 2: 9)
  - Dellums, Ronald, 1979 (Box-folder 2: 10)
  - DeRuyter, Mark, 1980 (Box-folder 2: 11)
  - Dietrich, R., 1973-1976 (Box-folder 2: 12)
  - Dittberner, Job, 1976 (Box-folder 2: 13)
  - Dodge, Ronald, 1966-1977 (Box-folder 2: 14)
  - Dodson, Christine, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 2: 15)
  - Dombroski, E., 1965 (Box-folder 2: 16)
  - Donaldson, Allyn, 1965 (Box-folder 2: 17)
  - Dornan, Robert, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 2: 18)
  - Downer, Elvin, 1973 (Box-folder 2: 19)
  - Drakoulis, Mary, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 2: 20)
  - Duncan, Betty, 1980 (Box-folder 2: 21)
  - Dunwell, R., 1971 (Box-folder 2: 22)
  - Elmore, Denise, 1973 (Box-folder 2: 23)
  - Elzy, Martin, 1979 (Box-folder 2: 24)
  - Ennis, Barbara, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 2: 25)
  - Evans, Daniel, 1959-1963 (Box-folder 2: 26)
  - Fabio, Caroline, 1979 (Box-folder 2: 27)
  - Fer, John, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 2: 28)
  - Ferguson, Lyn, 1978 (Box-folder 2: 29)
  - Fernandez, Angel, 1980 (Box-folder 2: 30)
  - Flynn, T., 1980 (Box-folder 2: 31)
  - Foley, Dermit, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 2: 32)
  - Foster, Louis, 1980 (Box-folder 2: 33)
  - Franklin, Larry, 1979 (Box-folder 2: 34)
  - Frazer, F., 1969 (Box-folder 2: 35)
  - Freed, M., 1966 (Box-folder 2: 36)
  - Fritch, R., 1967-1969 (Box-folder 2: 37)
  - Ganucheau, Gilbert, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 2: 38)
  - Gnall, J., 1967 (Box-folder 2: 39)
  - Goodman, Donald, 1982 (Box-folder 2: 40)
  - Goodson, J., 1969 (Box-folder 2: 41)
  - Gorder, Merle, 1965 (Box-folder 2: 42)
  - Gordon, Barbara, 1970 (Box-folder 2: 43)
  - Gorham, Ardith, 1982 (Box-folder 2: 44)
  - Gratch, A., 1967-1978 (Box-folder 2: 45)
  - Grattopp, Ronald, 1977 (Box-folder 2: 46)
  - Green, Kenneth, 1978 (Box-folder 2: 47)
  - Greene, G., 1965-1966 (Box-folder 2: 48)
  - Griffin, Darlene, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 2: 49)
  - Griffiths, Ann, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 2: 50)
  - Gude, Gilbert, 1974 (Box-folder 2: 51)
  - Gulyassy, Anne, 1980 (Box-folder 2: 52)
  - Hahn, Joseph, 1980 (Box-folder 3: 1)
  - Hall, Blair Parks, 1979 (Box-folder 3: 2)
  - Hall, Sam, 1979 (Box-folder 3: 3)
  - Hamilton, Larry, 1979 (Box-folder 3: 4)
  - Hammond, C., 1971 (Box-folder 3: 5)
  - Hargrave, W., 1967 (Box-folder 3: 6)
  - Hartness, Paula, 1978 (Box-folder 3: 7)
  - Hastings, B., 1968 (Box-folder 3: 8)
  - Hastings, James, 1979 (Box-folder 3: 9)
  - Hayakawa, S., 1979 (Box-folder 3: 10)
  - Heller, Bruce, 1977 (Box-folder 3: 11)
  - Hinkle, Charles, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 3: 12)
  - Holbrooke, Richard, 1977 (Box-folder 3: 13)
  - Holland, J., 1962 (Box-folder 3: 14)
  - Holt, R., 1973 (Box-folder 3: 15)
  - Holyoak, Marjorie, undated (Box-folder 3: 16)
  - Hopper, Earl, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 3: 17)
  - Howard, Dwight, 1972 (Box-folder 3: 18)
  - Huber, Nelson, 1966 (Box-folder 3: 19)
  - Hunter, G. William, 1980 (Box-folder 3: 20)
  - Hunter, H., 1966 (Box-folder 3: 21)
  - Hurst, James, 1979 (Box-folder 3: 22)
  - Intercity Express Publishing, 1979 (Box-folder 3: 23)
  - Jacobs, Richard, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 3: 24)
  - Johnson, Andrew, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 3: 25)
  - Johnson, J., 1971-1973 (Box-folder 3: 26)
  - Johnson, Linda, 1981 (Box-folder 3: 27)
  - Jones, Donald, 1980 (Box-folder 3: 28)
  - Kelly, Robert, 1979 (Box-folder 3: 29)
  - Kent, Adam, 1980 (Box-folder 3: 30)
  - Kidder, Kevin, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 3: 31)
  - Kilgore, J., 1979 (Box-folder 3: 32)
  - Kimmitt, Robert, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 3: 33)
  - King, Zelma, 1983 (Box-folder 3: 34)
  - Koepke, M., 1967 (Box-folder 3: 35)
  - Kopp, Robert, 1982 (Box-folder 3: 36)
  - Kohlizik, Cathy, 1974 (Box-folder 3: 37)
  - Labell, L., 1979 (Box-folder 3: 38)
  - LaFontaine, J., 1979 (Box-folder 3: 39)
  - Lambert, Thomas, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 3: 40)
  - Langford, F. Steele, 1980 (Box-folder 3: 41)
  - Lantos, Tom, 1982 (Box-folder 3: 42)
  - Larkin, Richard, 1980 (Box-folder 3: 43)
  - Lawrence, G., 1970 (Box-folder 3: 44)
  - Lee, Fitzhugh, 1961 (Box-folder 3: 45)
  - Lehman, John, 1983 (Box-folder 3: 46)
  - Lemke, W., 1968 (Box-folder 3: 47)
  - Levin, M., 1974-1978 (Box-folder 3: 48)
  - Lewis, Barbara, 1969-1983 (Box-folder 3: 49)
  - Lewis, Brian, 1977 (Box-folder 3: 50)
  - Lewis, Frank, 1965 (Box-folder 3: 51)
  - Lewis, Mary Jane, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 3: 52)
  - Lopez, Celina, 1984 (Box-folder 3: 53)
  - Luther, J., 1967-1973 (Box-folder 3: 54)
  - Lykins, Lidle, 1966 (Box-folder 3: 55)
  - Lyon, Scott, 1965 (Box-folder 3: 56)
  - MacArthur, Douglas, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 3: 57)
  - Macomber, William, 1969 (Box-folder 3: 58)
  - Manke, Paul, 1968 (Box-folder 3: 59)
  - Mansfield, Mike, 1965 (Box-folder 3: 60)
  - Marshall, M., 1976-1977 (Box-folder 4: 1)
  - Mather, Paul, 1979 (Box-folder 4: 2)
  - Matthes, Donald, 1980 (Box-folder 4: 3)
  - McCloskey, Robert, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 4: 4)
  - McDonald, Craig, 1972-1978 (Box-folder 4: 5)
  - McDonald, Kathryn, 1972 (Box-folder 4: 6)
  - McDonald, Kurt, 1977 (Box-folder 4: 7)
  - McDonald, Mickie, 1970-1980 (Box-folder 4: 8)
  - McNeil, T., 1974 (Box-folder 4: 9)
  - McNeill, C., 1972 (Box-folder 4: 10)
  - Miller, Cindy, 1983 (Box-folder 4: 11)
  - Mills, E., 1977 (Box-folder 4: 12)
  - Monaghan, Thomas, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 4: 13)
  - Montgomery, Gillepsie, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 4: 14)
  - Moore, J., 1965 (Box-folder 4: 15)
  - Moore, R., 1980 (Box-folder 4: 16)
  - Mount, Stuart, 1971 (Box-folder 4: 17)
  - Murphy, Dean, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 4: 18)
  - Myers, Gilbert, 1965 (Box-folder 4: 19)
  - National Human Rights Committee for POW-MIAs, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 4: 20)
  - National League of Families of American Prisoners and Missing in Southeast Asia, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 4: 21)
  - NeSmith, E. Archie, 1974 (Box-folder 4: 22)
  - Nixon, Richard, 1974 (Box-folder 4: 23)
  - Noble, B., 1979 (Box-folder 4: 24)
  - O'Daniel, Larry, 1980 (Box-folder 4: 25)
  - Odell, Deborah, 1966-1979 (Box-folder 4: 26)
  - Oksenberg, Michel, 1979 (Box-folder 4: 27)
  - Olshin, Lewis, 1980 (Box-folder 4: 28)
  - Orrick, William, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 4: 29)
  - Owens, George, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 4: 30)
  - Pate, R., 1959 (Box-folder 4: 31)
  - Perry, Stephen, 1980 (Box-folder 4: 32)
  - Pinckney, T., 1979 (Box-folder 4: 33)
  - Poillon, A., 1979 (Box-folder 4: 34)
  - Pond, Stanley, 1984 (Box-folder 4: 35)
  - Potter, Chas, 1980 (Box-folder 4: 36)
  - Powell, Sandy, 1983 (Box-folder 4: 37)
  - Price, W., 1965 (Box-folder 4: 38)
  - Putnam, Robert, 1982 (Box-folder 4: 39)
  - Ramsey, Henry, 1984 (Box-folder 4: 40)
  - Ramskill, C., 1975 (Box-folder 4: 41)
  - Reid, Gerald, 1965 (Box-folder 4: 42)
  - Reilly, Paul, 1967 (Box-folder 4: 43)
  - Roberts, Dean, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 4: 44)
  - Robinson, Wayne, 1978 (Box-folder 4: 45)
  - Ross, Thomas, 1979 (Box-folder 4: 46)
  - Royer, Bill, 1979 (Box-folder 4: 47)
  - Rush, T., 1973-1975 (Box-folder 4: 48)
  - Savige, Charles, 1980 (Box-folder 4: 49)
  - Schrader, R., 1978 (Box-folder 4: 50)
  - Schulze, Richard, 1971-1984 (Box-folder 4: 51)
  - Schwartz, Abba, 1965 (Box-folder 4: 52)
  - Scofield, Jack, 1980 (Box-folder 4: 53)
  - Scott, Hugh, 1975 (Box-folder 4: 54)
  - Seay, James, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 4: 55)
  - Seiberlich, C., 1979 (Box-folder 4: 56)
  - Semmes, B., 1965 (Box-folder 4: 57)
  - Shelton, Dorothy Marian, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 4: 58)
  - Shephard, Johanna, 1977 (Box-folder 4: 59)
  - Shields, Roger, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 4: 60)
  - Sheils, Peter, 1982 (Box-folder 4: 61)
  - Silijegovic, Kathleen, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 4: 62)
  - Silverbush, Ed, 1975 (Box-folder 4: 63)
  - Simpson, Phil, 1979 (Box-folder 5: 1)
  - Sisson, Winfield Wilbur, 1967-1983 (Box-folder 5: 2)
  - Skopera, Ronald, 1977 (Box-folder 5: 3)
  - Slutz, Robert, 1966 (Box-folder 5: 4)
  - Smith, Ann, 1980 (Box-folder 5: 5)
  - Smith, P., 1966 (Box-folder 5: 6)
  - Smyth, Rome, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 5: 7)
  - Sorrentino, H., 1974-1979 (Box-folder 5: 8)
  - Stennis, John, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 5: 9)
  - Stewart, William, 1965-1979 (Box-folder 5: 10)
  - Strawberry, Kenneth, 1979 (Box-folder 5: 11)
  - Strickland, Lee, 1980 (Box-folder 5: 12)
  - Svendsen, L., 1977-1980 (Box-folder 5: 13)
  - Taranto, Susan, 1979 (Box-folder 5: 14)
  - Taylor, C. Waitman, 1973 (Box-folder 5: 15)
  - Tighe, Eugene, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 5: 16)
  - Tkaczuk, F., 1979-1981 (Box-folder 5: 17)
  - Tower, John, 1979 (Box-folder 5: 18)
  - Trager, David, 1978 (Box-folder 5: 19)
  - Tremper, W., 1977 (Box-folder 5: 20)
  - Trowbridge, Charles, 1975-1979 (Box-folder 5: 21)
  - Trujillo, Rosemary, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 5: 22)
  - Trung, Ly Thai, 1979 (Box-folder 5: 23)
  - Underdal, Penny, 1981 (Box-folder 5: 24)
  - Underhill, Llana, 1980 (Box-folder 5: 25)
  - United States Government Bookstore, 1979 (Box-folder 5: 26)
  - Van Bokkelen, Jane, 1983 (Box-folder 5: 27)
  - Van Bokkelen, Jock, 1979 (Box-folder 5: 28)
  - Vercher, Rita, 1980 (Box-folder 5: 29)
  - Vettasa, S., 1966 (Box-folder 5: 30)
  - Vohden, Ray, 1978 (Box-folder 5: 31)
  - Walsh, William, 1981 (Box-folder 5: 32)
  - Weber, Bo Eric, 1979 (Box-folder 5: 33)
  - Weinig, J., 1973 (Box-folder 5: 34)
  - Weissgarber, Tony, 1980 (Box-folder 5: 35)
  - White, Floyd, 1965 (Box-folder 5: 36)
  - White, Roy, 1965 (Box-folder 5: 37)
  - Wilcox, Larry, 1981 (Box-folder 5: 38)
  - Wilson, Dot, 1979 (Box-folder 5: 39)
  - Wilson, Gene, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 5: 40)
  - Wilson, Louis, 1975 (Box-folder 5: 41)
  - Wilson, Robert, 1979 (Box-folder 5: 42)
  - Wolff, Lester, 1978 (Box-folder 5: 43)
  - Woods, W., 1966 (Box-folder 5: 44)
  - Wright, Anne, 1977 (Box-folder 5: 45)
  - Young, Jonathan, 1981 (Box-folder 5: 46)
  - Zweiben, Beverly, 1981 (Box-folder 5: 47)
  - Telegrams, 1966-1980 (Box-folder 5: 48)
- Government file, 1950-1982
  Scope and Contents note
  Contains memoranda, booklets, transmissions, and other printed matter related to various United States government agencies and branches of the American military, including material on the Freedom of Information Act.
  - Central Intelligence Agency, 1955-1980
    - 1955 (Box-folder 5: 49)
    - 1965 (Box-folder 5: 50)
    - 1966 (Box-folder 6: 1)
    - 1967 (Box-folder 6: 2-3)
    - 1968 (Box-folder 6: 4)
    - 1969 (Box-folder 6: 5)
    - 1970 (Box-folder 6: 6)
    - 1971 (Box-folder 6: 7)
    - 1972 (Box-folder 6: 8)
    - 1974 (Box-folder 6: 9)
    - 1975 (Box-folder 6: 10)
    - 1976 (Box-folder 6: 11)
    - 1977 (Box-folder 6: 12)
    - 1978 (Box-folder 7: 1)
    - 1979 (Box-folder 7: 2)
    - 1980 (Box-folder 7: 3)
    - Undated (Box-folder 7: 4)
  - Defense Intelligence Agency, 1965-1980
    - 1965 (Box-folder 7: 5)
    - 1967 (Box-folder 7: 6)
    - 1969 (Box-folder 7: 7)
    - 1971 (Box-folder 7: 8)
    - 1972 (Box-folder 7: 9)
    - 1973 (Box-folder 7: 10)
    - 1974 (Box-folder 7: 11)
    - 1975 (Box-folder 7: 12)
    - 1976 (Box-folder 7: 13-14)
    - 1977 (Box-folder 8: 1)
    - 1978 (Box-folder 8: 2)
    - 1979 (Box-folder 8: 3)
    - 1980 (Box-folder 8: 4)
    - Undated (Box-folder 8: 5)
  - Department of the Army, 1971-1979
    - 1971-1974 (Box-folder 8: 6)
    - 1979 (Box-folder 8: 7)
    - Undated (Box-folder 8: 8)
  - Department of Defense, 1960-1980
    - 1960 (Box-folder 8: 9)
    - 1962 (Box-folder 8: 10)
    - 1963 (Box-folder 8: 11)
    - 1965 (Box-folder 8: 12)
    - 1966 (Box-folder 8: 13)
    - 1967 (Box-folder 8: 14)
    - 1968 (Box-folder 8: 15)
    - 1969 (Box-folder 8: 16)
    - 1971 (Box-folder 8: 17)
    - 1972 (Box-folder 9: 1)
    - 1973 (Box-folder 9: 2)
    - 1974 (Box-folder 9: 3)
    - 1975 (Box-folder 9: 4)
    - 1976 (Box-folder 9: 5)
    - 1977 (Box-folder 9: 6)
    - 1978 (Box-folder 9: 7-8, Box 10, Box 11)
      Contains five manuals titled "Uncorrelated Information Relating to Missing Americans in Southeast Asia" in addition to loose documents.
    - 1979 (Box-folder 11: 1)
    - 1980 (Box-folder 11: 2)
    - Undated (Box-folder 12: 1-2)
  - Department of Justice, 1980 (Box-folder 12: 3)
  - Department of State, 1965-1981
    - 1965 (Box-folder 12: 4)
    - 1966 (Box-folder 12: 5)
    - 1967 (Box-folder 12: 6)
    - 1969 (Box-folder 12: 7)
    - 1971 (Box-folder 12: 8)
    - 1973 (Box-folder 12: 9)
    - 1974-1976 (Box-folder 12: 10)
    - 1977 (Box-folder 12: 11)
    - 1978 (Box-folder 12: 12)
    - 1979 (Box-folder 12: 13)
    - 1980-1981 (Box-folder 12: 14)
    - Undated (Box-folder 12: 15)
  - International Court of Justice, 1979 (Box-folder 12: 16)
  - National Archives and Records Service, 1979 (Box-folder 12: 17)
  - National Personnel Records Center, 1979 (Box-folder 12: 18)
  - National Security Agency, 1979 (Box-folder 12: 19)
  - National Security Council, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 12: 20)
  - United States Air Force, 1950-1982
    - 1950-1959 (Box-folder 12: 21)
    - 1961 (Box-folder 12: 22)
    - 1963 (Box-folder 12: 23)
    - 1964 (Box-folder 13: 1)
    - 1965 (Box-folder 13: 2-3)
    - 1966 (Box-folder 13: 4)
    - 1967 (Box-folder 13: 5)
    - 1968 (Box-folder 13: 6)
    - 1969 (Box-folder 13: 7)
    - 1970 (Box-folder 13: 8)
    - 1971 (Box-folder 13: 9)
    - 1972 (Box-folder 14: 1, Box-folder 13: 10)
    - 1973 (Box-folder 14: 2)
    - 1974 (Box-folder 14: 3)
    - 1975 (Box-folder 14: 4-5)
    - 1976 (Box-folder 14: 6)
    - 1977 (Box-folder 14: 7, Box 15)
      Contains four binders in addition to loose documents.
    - 1978 (Box-folder 16: 1-2)
    - 1979 (Box-folder 16: 3-4)
    - 1980 (Box-folder 16: 5-6, Box 17)
      Contains one binder in addition to loose documents.
    - 1981-1982 (Box-folder 17: 1)
    - Undated (Box-folder 17: 2)
  - United States District Court, 1980 (Box-folder 17: 3)
  - United States Marine Corps, 1959-1980
    - 1959 (Box-folder 17: 4)
    - 1960 (Box-folder 17: 5)
    - 1961 (Box-folder 17: 6)
    - 1962 (Box-folder 17: 7)
    - 1963 (Box-folder 17: 8)
    - 1964 (Box-folder 17: 9)
    - 1965 (Box-folder 17: 10)
    - 1966 (Box-folder 17: 11)
    - 1967 (Box-folder 17: 12)
    - 1968 (Box-folder 17: 13)
    - 1969 (Box-folder 17: 14)
    - 1970 (Box-folder 17: 15)
    - 1971 (Box-folder 17: 16)
    - 1972-1976 (Box-folder 17: 17)
    - 1977-1978 (Box-folder 17: 18)
    - 1979-1980 (Box-folder 17: 19)
    - Undated (Box-folder 17: 20)
  - United States Navy, 1957-1981
    - 1957 (Box-folder 17: 21)
    - 1958 (Box-folder 17: 22)
    - 1959 (Box-folder 17: 23)
    - 1960 (Box-folder 17: 24)
    - 1961 (Box-folder 17: 25)
    - 1962 (Box-folder 17: 26)
    - 1963 (Box-folder 17: 27)
    - 1964 (Box-folder 17: 28)
    - 1965 (Box-folder 18: 1)
    - 1966 (Box-folder 18: 2)
    - 1967 (Box-folder 18: 3-4)
    - 1968 (Box-folder 18: 5)
    - 1969 (Box-folder 18: 6)
    - 1970 (Box-folder 18: 7)
    - 1971 (Box-folder 18: 8)
    - 1972 (Box-folder 18: 9)
    - 1973 (Box-folder 18: 10)
    - 1974-1975 (Box-folder 18: 11)
    - 1976 (Box-folder 18: 12, Box-folder 19: 1-2)
    - 1977 (Box-folder 19: 3)
    - 1978 (Box-folder 19: 4)
    - 1979 (Box-folder 19: 5)
    - 1980 (Box-folder 19: 6)
    - 1981 (Box-folder 19: 7)
    - Undated (Box-folder 19: 8)
- Legal file, 1961-1984
  - Cases, 1961-1984
    - General, 1961-1978 (Box-folder 20: 1-3)
      Contains printed summaries of various court cases used for research purposes.
    - Darr v. Carter, 1981 (Box-folder 20: 4)
    - Fors v. Clayator et al, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 20: 5)
    - Hartness v. Carter, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 20: 6-7)
    - Hopper et al v. Carter, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 20: 8, Box-folder 21: 1-2)
    - Kane v. Carter, 1979 (Box-folder 21: 3)
    - Lewis v. Carter, 1980
      - Affidavits, 1980 (Box-folder 21: 4-5, Box-folder 22: 1)
      - Amendments, undated (Box-folder 22: 2)
      - Applications, 1980 (Box-folder 22: 3)
      - Briefs, 1980 (Box-folder 22: 4)
      - Interrogatories, 1980 (Box-folder 22: 5)
      - Memoranda, 1980 (Box-folder 22: 6)
      - Motions, 1980 (Box-folder 22: 7)
      - Notices, 1980 (Box-folder 22: 8)
      - Orders, 1980 (Box-folder 22: 9)
      - Proof of service, undated (Box-folder 22: 10)
      - Record excerpts, 1980 (Box-folder 22: 11)
      - Stipulations, 1980 (Box-folder 22: 12)
      - Summons, 1980 (Box-folder 22: 13)
      - Temporary restraining order, undated (Box-folder 22: 14)
    - Lewis v. Reagan, 1981 (Box-folder 22: 15)
    - Mateja v. Carter, 1979 (Box-folder 22: 16)
    - McDonald v. McLucas, 1974 (Box-folder 23: 1-3)
    - Newton v. Carter, 1979 (Box-folder 23: 4)
    - Poole v. Carter, 1979 (Box-folder 23: 5)
    - Sisson v. Carter, 1979-1981
      - Affidavits, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 23: 6, Box-folder 24: 1-4)
      - Briefs, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 24: 5)
      - Certificates, 1980 (Box-folder 25: 1)
      - Complaints, undated (Box-folder 25: 2)
      - Interrogatories, 1980 (Box-folder 25: 3)
      - Memoranda, 1980 (Box-folder 25: 4)
      - Motions, undated (Box-folder 25: 5)
      - Notices, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 25: 6)
      - Objections, 1981 (Box-folder 25: 7)
      - Oppositions, 1981 (Box-folder 25: 8)
      - Orders, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 25: 9)
      - Points, 1981 (Box-folder 25: 10)
      - Replies, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 25: 11)
      - Reports, 1980 (Box-folder 25: 12)
      - Responses, 1979 (Box-folder 25: 13)
      - Stipulations, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 25: 14)
      - Summons, 1979 (Box-folder 25: 15)
      - Transcripts, 1980 (Box-folder 26: 1)
    - Sisson Estate, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 26: 2)
    - Standerwick et al v. Carter, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 26: 3)
    - Townsend v. Carter, 1979 (Box-folder 26: 4)
  - Forms, 1980 (Box-folder 26: 5)
  - Hearings, 1979-1980
    - Statements, 1979 (Box-folder 26: 6)
    - Status review reports, 1980 (Box-folder 26: 7-8, Box-folder 27: 1-2)
    - Transcripts, undated (Box-folder 27: 3-4)
  - Power of Attorney, undated (Box-folder 28: 1)
  - Procedures, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 28: 2)
  - Miscellany, 1980 (Box-folder 28: 3)
    Contains untitled documents, proposals, worksheets, and other printed matter related to various court cases.
- Printed matter, 1965-1985
  - Clippings, 1965-1985
    - Undated-1965 (Box-folder 28: 4)
    - 1970-1979 (Box-folder 28: 5)
    - 1980-1985 (Box-folder 28: 6-7)
  - Financial records, 1967-1984
    Contains invoices, receipts, statements, and other printed matter related to the operations of the Law Offices of Walter E. Shjeflo.
    - Billing statements, 1978-1984 (Box-folder 28: 8-9, Box-folder 29: 1)
    - Invoices and receipts, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 29: 2)
    - Manuals, 1982 (Box-folder 29: 3)
    - Pay statements, 1967-1982 (Box-folder 29: 4)
  - Invitations, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 29: 5)
  - Maps, undated (Box-folder 29: 6)
  - Minutes, 1978 (Box-folder 29: 7)
  - Notes, undated (Box-folder 29: 8-14, Box-folder 30: 1-4)
  - Pamphlets, 1982 (Box-folder 30: 5)
  - Petitions, undated (Box-folder 30: 6)
  - Press releases, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 30: 7)
  - Reports, 1967-1984
    - House Select Committee on Missing Persons in Southeast Asia, 1977 (Box-folder 30: 8)
    - National League of Families, 1973-1984 (Box-folder 30: 9)
    - National League of Families of American Prisoners and Missing in Southeast Asia, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 30: 10)
    - Presidential Commission on Americans Missing and Unaccounted for in Southeast Asia, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 30: 11)
    - The Rand Corporation, 1969 (Box-folder 30: 12)